I don't like what‘s happening here!
我不喜欢这里发生的一切。
Well ,wait a minute ,let's try to use a feeling word
别激动，让我们尝试着描述下自己的感觉。
I’m pissed.
我很愤怒。
OK,pissed,why?
好的，愤怒，为什么？
Because no way should she be here.
因为她没理由要在这儿。
A ll right but tell her.
那你告诉她。
No way should you be here.
你不必在这里。
That's right. There's the rule. No use think. You broke it.
没错，这里有规矩，不能用逻辑思维，而你坏了规矩。
(I'm sorry)Sorry my ass,all you've done
since you got is sit around while the rest of us work our butts off
（抱歉）抱尼玛的歉，自打你来了，你就坐着没动，而我们一群人在苦口婆心。
and now you expect us to be glad that they let you stay.
现在他们让你继续待在这儿，你居然还指望我们能开开心心。
I'm not expect anything
我没要求任何事。
Gewn，just listening.Everybody，feeling word
格林，听就好了!诸位，描述自己的感受。
I don't thinking you are giving,
I don't feel that you are giving person.
我不认为你是在奉献，我不认为你是一个会奉献的人。
I’m trying
我在努力。
I'm don't thinking you have niceness ,
you see I don't feel niceness coming from you.
我不认为你是一个美好的人，我从你那儿感觉不到一丝美好。
should I just go to another group.
我是否要换个小组。
That's be a great idea,
you could spread your negativity even futher.(Daniel)
求之不得，你正好可以把你的负能量传播得更远。(丹尼尔）
You konw if you really try you can ruin the experience
for the entire patient population.
如果你真的努力，你可以毁掉所有病人的心情。
I'm having a bad day,
I'm having the worst damn day of my whole damn life.
该死的一天，这是我很丧的人生中最该死的一天。
So if it is not too much to ask of you people,
will you just back the fuck off
如果这个要求不过分的话，请你们滚蛋行吗？
Excellent work!Really excellent work!
非常棒，棒极了！
Good sharing everybody.
诸位，非常好的分享案例。